Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 1
  - Alphabetical files
    - Ampro Fund, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Ernest C. Arbuckle, 1970-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Arcs Foundation Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 1)
    - Sir Eric Ashby, 1972-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The Asia Foundation Correspondence, 1954-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Asia Foundation Purpose - Policies, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Asia Foundation Hong Kong Conference, 1966 Dec (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Asia Foundation and CIA, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Association of American Universities, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Atlantic Colleges, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - The Atlantic Council of the United States, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Jim Atwater, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ba, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Be, 1971-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bi, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bo, 1956-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Br, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bu, 1956-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Solomon R. Baker, 1970-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bechtel, 1959-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Jack Beck, 1957-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Arnold O. Beckman, 1970-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Danily Bell, 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Karl R. Bendetsen, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Bequest Program Appeal, 1980 Feb (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Peter Bing, 1969-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bing Family, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Boris, Kosta, 1960-1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - James G. Boswell/Boswell Foundation, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Boston Consulting Group (Bruce Henderson), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Boy Scounts of America National Council (Honorary), 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Alf E. Brandin, 1970-1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - John G Braun (Braun Family and Company), 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - British Consul-General, 1966-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - British-North American Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Brookings Institution, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - E. Howaes Brooks, 1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Robert Minge Brown, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - James E. Bryson, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Burlingame Country Club, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - W. Sherman Burns, 1969-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Joseph J. Burris, 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ca, 1956-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ch, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Co, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Cr, 1969-19850 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - California Academy of Sciences, 1930-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - California Club - Los Angeles, 1954-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Californians for Schools Proposition 1, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Canada - General, 1965-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - John D. Campbell, 1967-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Carnation Company Scholarship Foundation, 1963-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - R. Lynn Carroll, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Edward W. Carter, 1969-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - John Cassels, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Chandler Family and Company (Los Angeles), 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Ross H. Chamberlain, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Norton Clapp, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - James A. Clever, 1970-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Coe Bequest, 1955-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - George and Jennie Collins Foundation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Colonial Williamsburg, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Common Cause, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1953 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - The Commonwealth Fund, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Con Home - Stanford Children's Convalescent Hospital, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - James S. Copley, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - William Corbus, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - John C. Cosgrove, 1969-1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education - Corporate Luncheons, 1967-1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - S.H. Cowell Foundation, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - James F. Crafts, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Cresap, McCormick, and Paget, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Roy P. Crocker, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Crossett Funds, 1964-1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Nathan Cummings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Kenneth M. Cuthbertson, 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Da, 1969-1984 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Di, 1959-1984 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Dean Witter Reynolds, Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Christian De Guigne (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - F.W.D. Deakin, 1957-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Charles de Bretteville, 1969-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Comte Rene de Chambrun, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - R.W. deWeese, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Disputers, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Morris M. Doyle, 1971-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell G. Drake, 1970-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Lee A. DuBridge, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Charles E. Ducommun, 1970-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ben. C. Duniway, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - E, 1963-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - E.G. Edwards (Vice-Chancellor, University of Bradford), 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Marriner S. Eccles, 1970-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - John E. Elliott, 1968-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Northcutt Ely, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Energy Crisis, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - English-Speaking Union, 1964-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - The Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States -- Education Grants Board, 1956, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Fa, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Fi, 1963-1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Fo, 1959-1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Roy E. Fallas, M.D., 1969-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - The Family, 1953-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Garland R. Farmer, Jr., 1964, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - George Feyer, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - O.C. Field, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Fireman's Fund Insurance Company, 1952-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Firestone, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Harold H. Fisher, 1966-1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Max C. Fleischmann Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Tomas S. Fonacier, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - The Ford Foundation, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Foreign Relations Advisory Ctte., 1969-1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Carl M. Franklin, 1972-1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Dave Freeman, 1970-1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Kemper Freeman, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Fulton Freeman, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - The French Legion of Honor (American Society of), 1961-1976 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Paul S. Friedlander, 1970, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - W. P. Fuller Family, 1970-1985 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Ga, 1968-1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Go, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Gallo (Brothers and Foundation), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Charles W. Getchell, Jr., 1969-1983 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - J. Paul Getty, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Carl J. Gilbert, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Robert J. Glaser, M.D., 1971-1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. Roger Goodan, 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Grace Cathedral, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Thomas E. Gore, 1973-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cecil H. Green, 1968-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - R. Allen Griffin, 1969-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Z. Wayne Griffin, 1961-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Richard E. Guggenhime, 1968-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Tom Guidry (and his son, Albert), 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - David L. Guyer, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Ha, 1964-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - He, 1968-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ho, 1968-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Peter E. Haas, 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Walter A. Haas, Jr., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Walter A. Haas, Sr., 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Herbert L. Hahn, 1965-1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Michael L. Haider, 1965-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Paul R. Hanna, 1969-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Harkness Fellowships (of The Commonwealth Fund), 1971-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Godfrey Harris, 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The John A. Hartford Foundation, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - John W. Harvey, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Peyton Hawes, 1970-1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Sherman Hazeltine, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Hazel Hay, 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Julius D. Heldman, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Hearst Foundation, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Warner W. Henry, 1968-1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - A.J. Hettinger Jr., 1966-1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - William R. Hewlett, 1970-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - David B. Heyler, Jr., 1962-1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - John H. Hinrichs, 1969-1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Richard Hodgson, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - James E. Hollingsworth, 1968-1975 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Alberta, 1970 Oct 31 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Honorary Degrees - Harvard University, 1968 June 13 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Utah, 1968 June 6 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Honorary Degrees - Mills College (D.Hu.L.), 1967 Oct 18 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Honorary Degrees - McMaster University (Canada) (LL.D.), 1966 May 30 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Santa Clara (D.Hu.L.), 1963 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Honorary Degrees - Columbia University (LL.D.), 1962 June 5 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Honorary Degrees - Loyola University (L.A.) (LL.D.), 1961 June 11 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Denver (LL.D.), 1961 June 9 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Honorary Degrees - McGill University (LL.D.), 1961 May 31 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Southern California (LittD), 1960 June 9 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Honorary Degrees - Univ. California (LL.D.), 1958 June 13 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Honorary Degrees - Univ. British Columbia (LL.D.), 1958 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Caen (France) (D.Litt.), 1957 June 6 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Durham (England) (D.C.L.), 1953 July (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Honorary Degrees - University of Toronto (LL.D.), 1950 Oct 27 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Honorary Degrees - Univ. of San Francisco (LL.D.), 1950 June 4 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Herbert Hoover (General), 1952-1972 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Herbert Hoover Medal, 1968-1983 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Hoover House Inventory, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Herbert Hoover Birthplace Foundation and Heritage Foundation, 1954-1982 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Herbert Hoover Oral History Program, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Herbert Hoover (Monographs on), 1965, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Herbert Hoover Presidential Library Association, 1973-1974, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Herbert Hoover Boys' Clubs, 1965, 1973, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hoover Family, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Page Hufty, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Howard Hughes (all enterprises), 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Joseph D. Hughes, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Huntington Library henry E. huntington Library & Art Gallery, 1969-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - I, 1969-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Invitations To Serve Regretted, 1961-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Invitations to Serve (Honorary) Accepted, 1957-1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Invitations to Speak (Accepted), 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Invitations to Speak (Regretted), 1966-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Invitations (Social-Accepted), 1972-1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (Social-Regretted), 1972-1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Instituition of International Education, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - The James Irvine Foundation, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - J, 1970-1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - D.S. Jacobson, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Japan Society of San Francisco, 1959-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Robert Johnston (The Robert Johnston Company), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Thomas v. Jones, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - J.E. Jonsson, 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Ka, 1961-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Ki, 1959-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Andre Kanh-Wolf, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical Corporation-Board Matters, 1972-1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Edgar F. Kaiser, 1960-1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kaiser Family Foundation, 1968-1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Henry S. Kaplan, M.D., 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - J.M. kaplan Fund, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Katherine Branson School, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Virgil Kauffman, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Keck Family and Foundation, 1973-1974, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Barnaby C. Keeney, 1956-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Lawrence A. Kimpton, 1952-1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Wilmer H. Kingsford, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Joseph J Kinsella, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Grayson Kirk (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Daniel E. Koshland (Deceased 12/10/79) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - La (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Li (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Edwin H. Land (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ann Landers Column: Classroom Note-takers (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - George E. Lang (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Richard E. Lang (Deceased 11/6/82) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Marshall Laverty (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Legislation (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Douglass M. Leishman (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hans Leussink (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - The Leverhulme Trust Fund (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Roger Lewis (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Franklin A. Lindsay (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - John Litchfield (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - E. W. Littlefield (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - John L. Locke (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Sir Douglas Logan (1958-) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Lord Corporation (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles Dodgers (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Robert LUC (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Luce Foundation (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Ma (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Mc (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Me (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Mo (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Mr & Mrs Brian MacArthur (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Stuart Maclure (The Times Educational Supplement) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Makins (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Herbert Malarkey (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Bayless Manning (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Sir Herbert Marchant (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - The Louis B. Mayer Foundation (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Charles P. McCurdy, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Richard C. McCurdy (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - R. H. McDonnell (Died 10/12/80) (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Malcolm McDuffie (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Richard King Mellon Foundation (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Menlo School and College (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The Menninger Foundation (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Alice Merrill (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Harold A. Miller (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Shepard Mitchell (Deceased 9/79) (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - William L. Mitchell (and General Motors) (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - George S. Mizota (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - George Morell (Deceased 4/12/78) (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Seeley Mudd Foundation (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Charles Munro (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - F. Warren Munro (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Paul F. Murphy (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Na (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lyle M. Nelson (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ni (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - National Conference of Christians & Jews (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - National Planning Association (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - National War College (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - O (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Old Time Althetes Association (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Pa (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Po (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - The Pacific-Union Club - San Francisco (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - David Packard (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Palo Alto Club (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Palo Alto Office Center - Luncheon Club (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Edwin W. Pauley (Deceased 7/81) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - L. B. Pearson (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Baltzer Peterson (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. Hugh David Phillips (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Herman Phileger (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Charles M. Pigott (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Thomas P. Pike (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - John C. Pool (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Portrait (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Frank O. Prior (Deceased 1/18/84) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Eugene C. Pulliam (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Q-Rh (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Rainer (Indian Scholarships) (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Recommendations (A-G) (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Recommendations (H-M) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Recommendations (N-Z) (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - H. Leonard Richardson (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - David Rockefeller (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - John D. Rockefeller III (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - William Lister Rogers M.D. (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Leo Rosten (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Roth Family (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - C. Easton Rothwell (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - The Royal Horticultural Society (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Madeleine Hass Russell (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Knowles Ryerson (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Sa (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Se (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Si (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sp-Sta (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ste (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - San Fransisco International Music Competition Foundation (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - San Fransisco Opera (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Comission to Study - San Fransisco School System (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Scaife Family (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Schwabacher Family (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Fred Schwengel (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Scientific American (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Charles Craven Scott (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Joseph B. Scudder (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Shell Oil (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Talbot Shelton (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Lord Sherfield (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sierra Club (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Sigmund Stern Grove Music Festival Association (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Lord Sinclair of Cleve (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - G. Willard Somers (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - (Mr and) Mrs Gordon Southam (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Carl B. Spaeth (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Monroe E. Spaght (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - M. L. Spector (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Stanford Club of Los Angeles (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Stanford-In-Washington (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Peter Stansky (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Robert Stanton (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - John Stauffer (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Arthur C. Stewart (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Thomas M. Storke (Deceased) (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Sunset Club (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sunset Club - Speeches, etc. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Survey - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Harold W. Sweatt (Deceased 7/1/80) (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - H. Melvin Swift, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Benjamin H. Swig (Deceased 10/31/80) (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Theodore E. Swigart (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Gardiner Symonds (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Ta (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Paul Tabori (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - H. Stuart Taylor (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Hall Templeton (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Thacher School (Since 1964) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Joseph M. Thomas (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Lowell Thomas (and Lowell Thomas Jr.) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Thorne Family (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Severt W. Thurston (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Times Newspapers of Great Britain (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - William R. Timken, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - To (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Totterers (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Tridair Industries (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Tulane University - Board of Visitors (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Twilight Club (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - U (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - United Negro College Funds (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - University Club (Palo Alto) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - University Club (New York) (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - V (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Wa (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - We (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Wo (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Frank F. Walker (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Micheal H. Walsh (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Keene Watkins (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - T.R. Weaver (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Western Assn. Schools & Colleges (Accreditation -- UC Irvine) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Westover School (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Sir John Wheeler-Bennett (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Raymond B. White (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - White House Fellows (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - David Wills (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Mrs George A. Winzer (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Robert J. Woolsey, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Moffat Woodside (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - World Affairs Council of No. California 25th Anniversary Year (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Charles B. Wrightsman (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Dr. jur. Hans Wuttke (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - X-Y-Z (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Miscellaneous - Part 1 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Miscellaneous - Part 2 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Miscellaneous - Part 3 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Stanford Research Institute - International Committee (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - IIC Conferences (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - IIC - San Fransisco, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - IIC, 1973 Sep 17-21 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - International Industrial Conference - San Fransisco, 1969 Sep 15-19 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Long Range Planny Services (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - SRI - Relationship (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Board of Directors, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Research Institute - Board of Directors, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - United World Colleges - Also "Alantic Colleges" - Part 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - United World Colleges - Also "Alantic Colleges" - Part 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - United World Colleges - Also "Alantic Colleges" - Part 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Universities & Colleges - Misc. Part 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Universities & Colleges - Misc. Part 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - University of Alberta (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Brigham Young University (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - University of British Columbia (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - British Commonwealth Universities (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Brown University (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - University of California (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - University of California (re legislation: ACA '83) (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - University of California, Santa Cruz (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - University of California, Davis (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - California Institute of Technology (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Gonzaga University - Spokane, Washington (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Harvard University (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - University of Hawaii (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - International Christian University (Japan) (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - McMaster University (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Memorial University of Newfoundland (St. John's, Canada) (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - University of Saskatchewan (Regina Campus) (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - University of Toronto - Part 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - University of Toronto - Part 2 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - University of Toronto - Part 3 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - University of Toronto - Class of '27 (Victoria College), 1950s- (Box 10, Folder 30)